<LanguageData>
	<!-- _Translation\Grabbed_Defs_from_patches\prog patches0.xml -->
	                   <!-- EN: You have successfully completed enough pre-neolithic research projects and have advanced to neolithic tech level. This will allow you to pick a Cornerstone - a powerful bonus that applies only to your civilization. -->
	<VFET_FormTribe.description>Вы успешно завершили достаточное количество донеолитических исследовательских проектов и перешли на технологический уровень неолита. Это позволит вам выбрать Краеугольный камень — мощный бонус, действующий только на вашу цивилизацию.</VFET_FormTribe.description>
	                  <!-- EN: You have successfully completed enough neolithic research projects and have advanced to medieval tech level. This will allow you to pick a Cornerstone - a powerful bonus that applies only to your civilization. -->
	<VFET_FormTown.description>Вы успешно завершили достаточное количество исследовательских проектов эпохи неолита и перешли на технологический уровень средневековья. Это позволит вам выбрать Краеугольный камень — мощный бонус, действующий только на вашу цивилизацию.</VFET_FormTown.description>
	                  <!-- EN: You have successfully completed enough medieval research projects and have advanced to industrial tech level. This will allow you to pick a Cornerstone - a powerful bonus that applies only to your civilization. -->
	<VFET_FormCity.description>Вы успешно завершили достаточное количество исследовательских проектов эпохи средневековья и перешли на промышленный технологический уровень. Это позволит вам выбрать Краеугольный камень — мощный бонус, действующий только на вашу цивилизацию.</VFET_FormCity.description>
	                        <!-- EN: You have successfully completed enough industrial research projects and have advanced to spacer tech level. This will allow you to pick a Cornerstone - a powerful bonus that applies only to your civilization. -->
	<VFET_FormCollective.description>Вы успешно завершили достаточное количество исследовательских проектов промышленной эры и перешли на технологический уровень космической эры. Это позволит вам выбрать Краеугольный камень — мощный бонус, действующий только на вашу цивилизацию.</VFET_FormCollective.description>
	                   <!-- EN: You have successfully completed enough spacer research projects and have advanced to ultratech tech level. This will allow you to pick a Cornerstone - a powerful bonus that applies only to your civilization. -->
	<VFET_FormNexus.description>Вы успешно завершили достаточное количество исследовательских проектов космической эры и перешли на технологический уровень ультратехнологий. Это позволит вам выбрать Краеугольный камень — мощный бонус, действующий только на вашу цивилизацию.</VFET_FormNexus.description>
</LanguageData>